<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Sholok's Notes - CSS</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/feeds/css.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://sholok404.github.io/</id><updated>2017-03-10T04:00:00+06:00</updated><entry><title>Kaioken CSS - Probably King Kai's Favourite framework</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/kaioken-css-probably-king-kais-favourite-framework.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-10T04:00:00+06:00</published><updated>2017-03-10T04:00:00+06:00</updated><author><name>Syed Subeh-Sadik Sholok</name></author><id>tag:sholok404.github.io,2017-03-10:/kaioken-css-probably-king-kais-favourite-framework.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few days back, I was struggling with Bootstrap mainly because it was too kind
in the sense that it did too much for me. The problem I mainly faced with was
colouring; Bootstrap's navbars and other components already had a fixed color
and modifying something so advanced was pretty …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few days back, I was struggling with Bootstrap mainly because it was too kind
in the sense that it did too much for me. The problem I mainly faced with was
colouring; Bootstrap's navbars and other components already had a fixed color
and modifying something so advanced was pretty complicated. So, I decided watching
some Dragon Ball Z would be some great stress relief. I soon got bored rewatching
the same shit and so I decided to go back to coding and this is when I got the idea;
I could make my own framework! Because I was still in the mood of DBZ, I named
my framework Kaioken CSS in the sense that it would basically power up CSS functionalities
and could be used by everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically, Kaioken CSS is a no-nonsense CSS framework. It comes with a flexbox grid
system and some UI components like navbars and footers; however it is in no way a
UI framework. It only includes the layout for some common components so that the developers
can make their website however they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've published it under the MIT license and put it up on Github. I've also documented
it and put up some contribution guidelines. You'd probably want to check it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github repo: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wiki: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documentationn: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki/Documentation"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki/Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content></entry></feed>