<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Sholok's Notes - Syed Subeh-Sadik Sholok</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/feeds/syed-subeh-sadik-sholok.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://sholok404.github.io/</id><updated>2017-11-06T03:17:00+06:00</updated><entry><title>Hosting Your Pelican Website in Github Pages</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/hosting-your-pelican-website-in-github-pages.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-11-06T03:17:00+06:00</published><updated>2017-11-06T03:17:00+06:00</updated><author><name>Syed Subeh-Sadik Sholok</name></author><id>tag:sholok404.github.io,2017-11-06:/hosting-your-pelican-website-in-github-pages.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hosting Pelican websites can be pretty complicated; there is not a lot
of documentation about it. This is why I am writing this article. Also, I am assuming
you already have built a website using Pelican. Also make sure to delete the output
directory before proceeding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started, create …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hosting Pelican websites can be pretty complicated; there is not a lot
of documentation about it. This is why I am writing this article. Also, I am assuming
you already have built a website using Pelican. Also make sure to delete the output
directory before proceeding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get started, create two repositories. One of them should be named &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt;.
Name the other one whatever you want. Then add the first repo as the origin of the
root of your project. Use this: &lt;code&gt;git remote add origin &amp;lt;url-of-repo&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. Replace the part
in '&amp;lt;&amp;gt;'s with your repository's url. Then, add your &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt; repository
as a submodule in the output directory. For this, use &lt;code&gt;git submodule add &amp;lt;url-of-repo&amp;gt; output&lt;/code&gt;.
Then, build your website using &lt;code&gt;pelican -s pelicanconf.py&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, first add, commit and push all the files to its repository. Then navigate
to the output directory and do the same. You should have your website up and running in
a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Kaioken CSS - Probably King Kai's Favourite framework</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/kaioken-css-probably-king-kais-favourite-framework.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-10T04:00:00+06:00</published><updated>2017-03-10T04:00:00+06:00</updated><author><name>Syed Subeh-Sadik Sholok</name></author><id>tag:sholok404.github.io,2017-03-10:/kaioken-css-probably-king-kais-favourite-framework.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few days back, I was struggling with Bootstrap mainly because it was too kind
in the sense that it did too much for me. The problem I mainly faced with was
colouring; Bootstrap's navbars and other components already had a fixed color
and modifying something so advanced was pretty …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few days back, I was struggling with Bootstrap mainly because it was too kind
in the sense that it did too much for me. The problem I mainly faced with was
colouring; Bootstrap's navbars and other components already had a fixed color
and modifying something so advanced was pretty complicated. So, I decided watching
some Dragon Ball Z would be some great stress relief. I soon got bored rewatching
the same shit and so I decided to go back to coding and this is when I got the idea;
I could make my own framework! Because I was still in the mood of DBZ, I named
my framework Kaioken CSS in the sense that it would basically power up CSS functionalities
and could be used by everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically, Kaioken CSS is a no-nonsense CSS framework. It comes with a flexbox grid
system and some UI components like navbars and footers; however it is in no way a
UI framework. It only includes the layout for some common components so that the developers
can make their website however they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've published it under the MIT license and put it up on Github. I've also documented
it and put up some contribution guidelines. You'd probably want to check it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github repo: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wiki: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documentationn: &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki/Documentation"&gt;https://github.com/sholok404/kaioken-css/wiki/Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>WEB DEVELOPMENT AND CLICKING BUTTONS AREN'T THE SAME THING!</title><link href="https://sholok404.github.io/web-development-and-clicking-buttons-arent-the-same-thing.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-06T04:40:00+06:00</published><updated>2017-03-06T04:40:00+06:00</updated><author><name>Syed Subeh-Sadik Sholok</name></author><id>tag:sholok404.github.io,2017-03-06:/web-development-and-clicking-buttons-arent-the-same-thing.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;So.....My first blog post is already out of topic from my usually geeky
stuff. Basically, this is me complaining about my parents thinking web development
is easy stuff. If you didn't already know, I have been programming since I was
7 so I am pretty good at this stuff …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So.....My first blog post is already out of topic from my usually geeky
stuff. Basically, this is me complaining about my parents thinking web development
is easy stuff. If you didn't already know, I have been programming since I was
7 so I am pretty good at this stuff. I built my first website when I was about
7 and a half so I got some spotlight among family members but recently my cousin, who is 13,
managed to do the same thing however, he didn't really code anything. He used
one of those web site builders; you know like &lt;a href="http://www.simplesite.com/"&gt;SimpleSite&lt;/a&gt;.
Although I appreciate his efforts, my problem was that my parents thought that
MAKING &lt;a href="https://sholok404.github.io/digital-agency-theme/"&gt;THIS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://github.com/sholok404/srl-marine-products/"&gt;THIS&lt;/a&gt;
IS SIMPLE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is all I have to say. If a close relative of a programmer is reading this,
please try to appreciate him/her; it requires a lot of effort.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>